boatshed.com 2014-06-27

# Privacy Policy | Boatshed.com

  * Home /
  * Privacy Policy

##  What we collect and how we use it

Boatshed.com take the protection of privacy very seriously, and we do our upmost to protect it. Boatshed.com asks that customers supply certain personal data when registering to use our services, this data is used only for the purpose of communicating with our customers.

##  Cookies

We may use small text files called cookies to improve user experience. Boatshed.com's cookies are simple text files used only to identify the customer; they do not capture any personal information from your computer or store any sensitive data.

##  Sharing Personal Information

Boatshed.com may share your personal information with partners or suppliers for the purposes of fulfilling an order or subscription. This may include third party suppliers, companies used to process credit card or other payment types, provide customer service, or otherwise provide services that enable us to serve you. These organizations will have access only to the information required to permit them to perform their obligations to us.

Beyond the aforementioned personal information disclosures, Boatshed.com will only disclose additional information if required by law, regulation, or other government authority, to prevent harm to our company, affiliate companies, clients, or anyone else to protect against fraud. We may transfer your personally identifiable information to a successor entity upon a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which Boatshed.com participates or to a purchaser of all or substantially all of Boatshed.com's assets. Such successor entity shall be bound by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

##  Links to Third Party Sites

The Boatshed.com websites may be linked to other websites on the Internet which are not under the control of or maintained by Boatshed.com. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by Boatshed.com of those other web sites, the content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith. You acknowledge that Boatshed.com is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and you agree that Boatshed.com is not responsible for the content of such sites. Your use of these other linked web sites is subject to the respective terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked sites.

##  Security

Boatshed.com employs procedural and technological measures, consistent with the demands of customer service. Such measures are reasonably designed to protect your personally identifiable information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. Where reasonably practical, Boatshed.com uses encryption, password protection, firewalls, internal restrictions and other security measures to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

##  Updating Your Information

Your information may be updated at any time, please see our contact page for details of how to contact us.

##  Policy Changes

Boatshed.com reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time without public announcement. Clients and affiliates of Boatshed.com are encouraged to review this Privacy Policy on a regular basis.
